don't you know who we are cno professor i don't
nursah
the same nate you flew for
ach e
she rere erte
i heard they shut you downer refusing to drop bombs from stratuspery on te starving people
e when they realized that killing out the creople was not a long-term solution and they needed i back in secrets
i think it because public opinion wouldn't allow spending on space exporation
oyou know my father professor vean
not when yu're struggling to put food on the table
week seven years ago okra this year
now ite's just corn
a wer growing more than we half up with likely er potatoes in ireland in tewes
at in the dust po
the corn
wi'll die
se
in the letter